<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Lentigo.Net</title>
    <link>https://lentigo.net/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Lentigo.Net</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://lentigo.net/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Checking Out Docker</title>
      <link>https://lentigo.net/post/2015-06-06-checking-out-docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lentigo.net/post/2015-06-06-checking-out-docker/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve removed most of the software installed by Homebrew on my Mac and am going to give Docker a try for things like hosting databases and software development environments. One of these days I hope to jettison my server and use container environments to host sites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rapid Spring</title>
      <link>https://lentigo.net/post/2013-04-10-rapid-spring/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lentigo.net/post/2013-04-10-rapid-spring/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s some pictures from the garden in front of our house.
  Daffodils and Tulips 1     Daffodils and Tulips 2   I don&amp;rsquo;t think they are going to last very long. It&amp;rsquo;s gone from winter to summer in about a week here in DC &amp;hellip; snow on the ground two weeks ago and it&amp;rsquo;s supposed to get close to 90F here later today!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Move to Jekyll/Octopress</title>
      <link>https://lentigo.net/post/2013-04-02-move-to-jekyll-slash-octopress/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lentigo.net/post/2013-04-02-move-to-jekyll-slash-octopress/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve spent the last several days converting this site from &lt;a href=&#34;http://drupal.org&#34;&gt;Drupal&lt;/a&gt; to
&lt;a href=&#34;http://octopress.org&#34;&gt;Octopress&lt;/a&gt;.  I&amp;rsquo;ve done this for several reasons:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgraded to Drupal 5.1</title>
      <link>https://lentigo.net/node/15/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 23:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lentigo.net/node/15/</guid>
      <description>As part one of attempting to get back to blogging at this site I&amp;rsquo;ve upgraded it from Drupal 4.7 to Drupal 5.
The old theme was quite ugly so I switched the system default to Drupal&amp;rsquo;s Garland theme and changed the colors to that sort of mix of sunburn and suntan than Lentigo suggests! This looks better than the themes I&amp;rsquo;ve come up with in the past so I think I&amp;rsquo;ll stick with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April 9th, Evening</title>
      <link>https://lentigo.net/node/20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 22:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lentigo.net/node/20/</guid>
      <description>Some wins and losses this evening. On the losing side was my last SANS class. I&amp;rsquo;ve been taking their SANS+S course for preparation to take the CISSP exam. This particular class is taught on-line using a Java-based classroom product called Elluminate. It&amp;rsquo;s always taken a bit of work to start it up on my PowerBook and I generally expect to have to kill and restart it a few times before it gets a good connection back to the mothership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How long will it take to guess your password?</title>
      <link>https://lentigo.net/node/18/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 22:19:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lentigo.net/node/18/</guid>
      <description>I came across Bruce Schneier&amp;rsquo;s article on choosing secure passwords some time ago but just reread it again. I find the description of the efforts that AccessData&amp;rsquo;s PRTK goes through to guess a password fascinating. Once of the things they teach in security classes is that brute force attacks will always work; the only protection is in the amount of time it will take to succeed. Throw a little intelligence into the guessing and that amount of time can get very short!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer language studies in Arlington</title>
      <link>https://lentigo.net/node/21/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 20:07:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lentigo.net/node/21/</guid>
      <description>Arlington County Public Schools will offer beginning Arabic and Chinese language courses this summer. We could have more Arabic speakers in our high school next year than the either the US Dept of State or the FBI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scarier than The Master...</title>
      <link>https://lentigo.net/node/10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 18:12:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lentigo.net/node/10/</guid>
      <description>The clueless-ness of big content owners is just amazing...  Fox shuts down Buffy Hallowe&#39;en musical despite Whedon&#39;s protests: Cory Doctorow: Fox has shuit down a plan to perform a fan version of the Buffy musical episode, Once More with Feeling, even though creator Joss Whedon has asked them not to. Jason Schultz has written a great analysis of this here.  Is this the kind of copyright policy we want?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trusted Computing</title>
      <link>https://lentigo.net/node/13/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 18:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lentigo.net/node/13/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holiday Shopping Almost Done</title>
      <link>https://lentigo.net/node/23/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 14:53:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lentigo.net/node/23/</guid>
      <description>December 22nd and most of my shopping is done. I hate doing this stuff at the last minute but I do it every year so I must not hate it enough.
I had an interesting experience last night while shopping. Early in the evening I received an TXT message from my one of my monitoring sites indicating that our production server was down. After having great experiences with Debian servers over the last couple of years this box had experienced some heartburn from a recent kernel update and I figured the burn might have returned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Collectors of Hip</title>
      <link>https://lentigo.net/node/19/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 14:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lentigo.net/node/19/</guid>
      <description>Hope just sent me a link to the LOC&amp;rsquo;s Full National Recording Registry of the National Recording Preservation Board. I think the contents are as hip as one can get and I&amp;rsquo;m going to see how many of these I can find on Rhapsody and build a few choice playlists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What does your printer say about you?</title>
      <link>https://lentigo.net/node/9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 13:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lentigo.net/node/9/</guid>
      <description>Here&#39;s something to be aware of:  EFF cracks hidden snitch codes in color laser prints: Many color laser printers hide information about your printer&#39;s serial number and the date and time of your print job in every job you print. It&#39;s believed that this is done to get your equipment to incriminate you without your knowledge. Now EFF has decoded the information-hiding scheme on the Xerox Docucolor series, by getting EFF supporters to print out pages from their printers and mail them to our researchers, who examined them under magnification and special light and cracked the code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fix ssh-agent after installing Apple&#39;s 2008-005 security update</title>
      <link>https://lentigo.net/node/25/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 13:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lentigo.net/node/25/</guid>
      <description>After installing Apple&amp;rsquo;s 2008-005 security update on my Leopard machines I found that ssh-agent was no longer being started on system boot. I use ssh with key-based authentication for lots of things and not having it automatically loaded and communicating with my keychain was a real pain. After monkeying around with lots of ways to get it going again I found the following command, entered in a terminal and followed by a reboot, did the trick:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dia de los Muertos</title>
      <link>https://lentigo.net/node/12/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 13:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lentigo.net/node/12/</guid>
      <description>We put together the following altar to celebrate family and friends passed&amp;hellip;
  Our Dia de los Muertos Altar   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hmm, this place is dead...</title>
      <link>https://lentigo.net/node/24/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 12:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lentigo.net/node/24/</guid>
      <description>Okay, so I&amp;rsquo;ve not been good at keeping up here. I do plan on writing up more stuff soon, though. I&amp;rsquo;ve been studying for my GIAC GSEC re-cert and have come across a few ideas for things to research and write about after I take the test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My latest toy - the Nokia N800</title>
      <link>https://lentigo.net/node/16/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 00:41:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lentigo.net/node/16/</guid>
      <description>I picked up a new toy for myself for this last holiday season, a Nokia N800 Internet Tablet. It&amp;rsquo;s very cool. I bought it mainly to listen to streaming media and to keep up with e-mail and RSS feeds when not at my computer &amp;ndash; which so far means lying in bed.
The experience has been pretty good so far. I&amp;rsquo;ve moved all off my personal e-mail and feed reading to Google services, which offer plain XHTML interfaces if you know how to find them, and they work really well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ahh, Back...</title>
      <link>https://lentigo.net/node/22/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 00:32:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lentigo.net/node/22/</guid>
      <description>And newly moved from my old MediaTemple GS back to my trusty Linode. I like the Linode much better. Now to get to work on a theme for this site so these bi-annual posts will look nicer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back to Ecto</title>
      <link>https://lentigo.net/node/7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lentigo.net/node/7/</guid>
      <description>Well, the test with MarsEdit didn&amp;rsquo;t go very well so we&amp;rsquo;re back to using Ecto for blogging. It seems to integrate much better with other Mac apps so I&amp;rsquo;ll just need to learn how to sort out its quirks.
BTW, I&amp;rsquo;m trying to get into the habit of blogging more, really!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hope, Aaron and Jeffrey on KDH</title>
      <link>https://lentigo.net/node/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lentigo.net/node/5/</guid>
      <description>Hope, Aaron and Jeffrey on the beach in KDH, Summer 2005   Here&amp;rsquo;s a picture of Hope, Aaron and Jeffrey on the beach in Kill Devil Hills, NC. This was taken on our last beach day of our 2005 summer vacation. &amp;hellip;s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stuff I Like</title>
      <link>https://lentigo.net/node/8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lentigo.net/node/8/</guid>
      <description>Now that I spend about 90 minutes on the train each day I&#39;ve been listening to a lot of podcasts during my commute. My favorite, by far, is the Evil Genius Chronicles. Good stories, excellent music, and great attitude, Dave rocks! If anybody actually reads this page they should go there, listen to a few podcasts, and buy the stuff package.  My Powerbook. After a couple of decades of using Windows and Linux laptops I switched about six months ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testing Ecto</title>
      <link>https://lentigo.net/node/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lentigo.net/node/4/</guid>
      <description>This is a test entry made with Ecto. I’m attaching a picture of the family taken toward the end of our recent OBX vacation to see how it posts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>